https://www.totaldebtfreedom.ca/privacy-policy/

Total Debt Freedom - Privacy Policy
Total Debt Freedom
My WordPress Blog
(866) 833 3055Friendly, Helpful, Service, 24/7. Call us now:
back
What are you looking for?
Privacy PolicyYou are here:HomePrivacy Policy
Total Debt Freedom Inc. (“Total Debt Freedom”) is committed to full compliance with federal, provincial, and local laws concerning online privacy. The company recognizes the need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) provided by persons who access the Total Debt Freedom’s web site. Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address, an email address or other contact information, whether at work or at home. In general, users can access the web site without revealing any Personal Information. If a user provides Personal Information, Total Debt Freedom may transfer that information across borders and from the user’s country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. Total Debt Freedom is committed to comply with all applicable laws that are designed to regulate the transmission and distribution of this information.
If Personal Information is disclosed to Total Debt Freedom on its web site, the company intends to take reasonable and appropriate steps, as may be required by applicable laws, to protect the Personal Information shared with the company from unauthorized access or disclosure. Total Debt Freedom may elect to update or correct that information. Total Debt Freedom will make reasonable efforts to incorporate updates and corrections in Personal Information provided by the user, as may be required by law.
Information obtained by Total Debt Freedom may be used to help deliver programs, products, information and services, maintain its web site and mailing lists, develop and market new products and services, or for other lawful purposes. Total Debt Freedom is committed to compliance with applicable laws concerning distribution of information to third parties.
Total Debt Freedom is committed to compliance with applicable laws dealing with online privacy. By using this web site, the user consents to the terms of the Online Privacy Policy and collection and processing by Total Debt Freedom of Personal Information. User acknowledges that Total Debt Freedom cannot guarantee or warrant the complete privacy and protection of Personal Information provided.
Although we currently do not employ the use of “cookies” some of the Total Debt Freedoms web pages may utilize “cookies” and other tracking technologies in the future. A “cookie” is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about web site activity. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by a web user. Most browsers allow a user to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. A user can set most browsers to notify the user if it has received a cookie, or a user may choose to block cookies with the browser. Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; click stream patterns; and dates and times that the web site is accessed. Total Debt Freedoms’ use of cookies and other tracking technologies provides information that may be used to improve the web site and the user’s web experience. The company may also analyze information for trends and statistics.
Price, terms, specifications, and availability are subject to change without notice. Total Debt Freedom Inc. trademarks are indicated. Other marks are the property of their respective owners.
Ask Us Anything
Strictly Confidential
Email Address
*
Question
*
Enter your question
Please leave this blank
If you are human, leave this field blank.
CategoriesBankruptcyCEO Richard CooperCollection AgenciesConsumer ProposalCredit CardsCredit CounsellingCustomer ServiceDebt SettlementGiving BackHousehold IdeasMoney & BudgetingMotivationSaving MoneyUS Based Debt Settlement Companies
Freedom Stories
We were sceptical at first, but Total Debt Freedom soon delivered as promised. Four out of five debts are now gone and we feel like we have been making real progress to our debt freedom date and given some real solid advice.
Al & JulieLondon, ON
After being absent for years, a smile has finally returned to our faces. Thank-you, you are so wonderful. We are so pleased that we are debt free and can resume our life again.
Jennifer & SeanOttawa, ON
Thanks for your hard work, it only took me 4 weeks to be debt free and the results were incredible. The creditors stopped calling almost immediately and I saved over $54,000. I sleep much better at night now.
DougToronto, On
It feels great knowing that I can finally go to the mailbox and actually enjoy picking up the mail not having to worry about threatening letters. I can even start answering my phone again knowing it won’t be someone on the other end asking me for money. I will always recommend TDF to anyone who is going through financial struggles.
Manuela
Home Trust Secured Visa
Establish credit if you have no credit history
Rebuild your credit
Virtually EVERYONE is approved
Apply Now
START LIVING DEBT FREE TODAY - CLICK HERE!
About Total Debt FreedomTotal Debt Freedom was founded in 2004 and is fully licensed and bonded. We are a next-generation debt relief company, with the goal of being recognized in Canada as a top provider of consumer credit card debt relief.
Local: (416) 855-0500
FREE Consultation: (866) 833-3055
All Other inquiries: (866) 833-1992Find us on:FacebookTwitterYouTubeInstagramLatest from the BlogHow To Get Your Kids To Start SavingJune 15, 2016When You Should Give Zero Fucks About DebtOctober 13, 2015How To Save Money & Brew Your Own BeerSeptember 21, 2015Debt Relief OptionsTDF Debt SettlementCredit Card Debt Relief OptionsDebt Consolidation LoanBankruptcyCredit CounsellingFAQ’sDebt Learning CentreHow to Stop Collection CallsHow to Stop Collection Calls – 2Get Out of Debt, the SecretHow to Settle Debt for Half of What You Owe, and Do it in 30 DaysSimple Tips for Great Credit
© 2015 TotalDebtFreedom.ca All rights reserved.
Privacy Policy
Terms and Conditions
Careers
Contact Us
Bottom Menu
Individual results will vary. Total Debt Freedom Inc. does not assume or pay any debt, nor does it provide legal advice or offer credit repair. If you need legal advice, you must consult with a licensed attorney. Individual results are highly dependant on successful completion of program and your ability to save funds. Settlement estimates of 40 - 60% are examples of past performance and are not intended to be a guarantee of future settlement results. Results will vary based on individual circumstances. Please read and understand all contract terms prior to enrolment.
Want to learnhow to cut your debt by 50% &get debt free in 3 years?
Yes, lets do this
No, I'm fine thanks
